Records of the National Society Of New England Women, 1895-1988
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES X. COLONIES
  - AUGUSTA, ME COLONY
    - General, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - BALTIMORE, MD COLONY
    - General, by-laws, undated (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Officers, Treasurer, financial records, 1955-1963 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - BOSTON, MA COLONY
    - General, history, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - minutes, 1919-1928 (Box 80, Folder 17)
        - 1928-1932 (Box 80, Folder 18)
        - 1932-1936 (Box 80, Folder 19)
        - 1937-1944 (Box 80, Folder 20)
        - 1954, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 21)
        - 1958-1968 (Box 80, Folder 22)
        - 1966-1969 (Box 80, Folder 23)
      - photograph, 1941 (Box 80, Folder 24)
      - programs, 1925 (Box 80, Folder 25)
      - receipt of gift, 1931 (Box 80, Folder 26)
      - scrapbooks, 1921-1923, 1926-1933, 1932-1939, 1939-1955 (Box 80, Folder 27)
      - yearbooks, 1930, 1943, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Officers, General, reports, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 29)
      - Registrar, correspondence, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 30)
        - membership lists, 1959-1970, undated (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Boards, Executive Board, minutes, 1919-1928 (Box 81, Folder 32)
      - 1928-1933 (Box 81, Folder 33)
      - 1933-1938 (Box 81, Folder 34)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - BRONXVILLE, NY COLONY
    - General, constitution and by-laws, 1938, 1968, 1975, undated (Box 81, Folder 36)
      - histories, 1914-1952 (Box 81, Folder 37)
      - memorabilia, 1945, 1956, undated (Box 81, Folder 38)
      - minutes, 1926-1935 (Box 81, Folder 39)
        - 1935-1941 (Box 81, Folder 40)
        - 1946-1948 (Box 81, Folder 41)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 81, Folder 42)
        - 1951 (Box 81, Folder 43)
        - 1952 (Box 81, Folder 44)
        - 1953 (Box 81, Folder 45)
        - 1953-1957 (Box 81, Folder 46)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 82, Folder 47)
        - 1955-1961 (Box 82, Folder 48)
        - 1958-1961 (Box 82, Folder 49)
        - 1962-1966 (Box 82, Folder 50)
        - 1966-1969 (Box 82, Folder 51)
        - 1969-1974 (Box 82, Folder 52)
      - reports, 1969-1974 (Box 82, Folder 53)
        - 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 54)
        - 1974-1980 (Box 82, Folder 55)
      - reports, 1977-1980 (Box 82, Folder 56)
      - programs, 1926-1980 (Box 82, Folder 57)
      - scrapbooks, 1914-1952, 1934-1935, 1952-1955, 1971-1974 (Box 83, Folder 58)
        - 1937-1946 (Box 83, Folder 59)
        - 1946-1952 (Box 83, Folder 60)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1954, 1974-1976 (Box 83, Folder 61)
      - President, correspondence, 1936-1960, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 62)
      - Registrar, correspondence, 1928-1980, undated (Box 83, Folder 63)
        - membership lists, 1914-1979 (Box 83, Folder 64)
        - annual reports and membership lists, 1927-1950 (Box 83, Folder 65)
  - BROOKLYN, NY COLONY
    - General, minutes, 1905-1906 (Box 84, Folder 66)
      - 1906-1907 (Box 84, Folder 67)
      - 1907-1922 (Box 84, Folder 68)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 84, Folder 69)
      - 1926-1927 (Box 84, Folder 70)
      - 1934-1936 (Box 84, Folder 71)
      - 1937-1939 (Box 84, Folder 72)
      - 1939-1941 (Box 84, Folder 73)
      - 1941-1944 (Box 84, Folder 74)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 85, Folder 75)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 85, Folder 76)
      - 1947-1948 (Box 85, Folder 77)
    - Officers, Registrar,membership list, 1914-1936 (Box 85, Folder 78)
    - Boards, Executive Board, minutes, 1907-1916 (Box 85, Folder 79)
      - 1916-1922 (Box 85, Folder 80)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 85, Folder 81)
      - 1928-1929 (Box 85, Folder 82)
      - 1931-1933 (Box 85, Folder 83)
      - 1933-1935 (Box 85, Folder 84)
      - 1964-1972 (Box 85, Folder 85)
  - BUFFALO, NY COLONY
    - General, charter, 1902 (Box 86, Folder 86)
    - Officers, Registrar, membership list, 1901-c.1910 (Box 86, Folder 87)
  - BURLINGTON, IA COLONY
    - General, minutes, 1930-1941 (Box 86, Folder 88)
      - 1942-1952 (Box 86, Folder 89)
      - scrapbook, 1932-1970 (Box 86, Folder 90)
        - enclosures, 1932-1970 (Box 86, Folder 91)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 92)
  - CALIFORNIA POPPY, CA COLONY
    - General, by-laws, history, 1972-1977 (Box 86, Folder 93)
    - Officers, Registrar, membership lists, 1977, undated (Box 86, Folder 94)
  - CAMBRIDGE, NY COLONY
    - General, charter, undated (Box 86, Folder 95)
  - CAPE COD, MA COLONY
    - Officers, Registrar, annual report, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 96)
  - CHAMPAIGN-URBANA, IL COLONY
    - General, charter, 1936 (Box 86, Folder 97)
  - CLEVELAND, OH COLONY
    - General, charter, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 98)
  - COLUMBUS, OH COLONY
    - General, by-laws, organizing minutes, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 99)
  - DETROIT, MI COLONY
    - Officers, Registrar, membership list, 1924-1946 (Box 86, Folder 100)
  - ELIZABETH, NJ COLONY
    - General, charter, 1928 (Box 86, Folder 101)
    - Officers, Registrar, membership list, 1928-1949 (Box 86, Folder 102)
  - ELIZABETH ALDEN, PA COLONY
    - General, minutes, 1953-1964 (Box 86, Folder 103)
      - 1964-1975 (Box 86, Folder 104)
    - Officers, Treasurer, financial records, 1953-1972 (Box 86, Folder 105)
  - ELIZABETH CHASE FOWLER, CA COLONY
    - General, by-laws, organizational papers, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 106)
  - ELIZABETH GLOVER DUNSTER, WA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 107)
  - ERIE, PA COLONY
    - General, Subjects, Perry Memorial House, undated (Box 87, Folder 108)
  - EUNICE MATHER WILLIAMS, IN COLONY
    - General, by-laws, organizational papers, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 109)
  - EVANSTON, IL COLONY
    - General, by-laws, 1948, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 110)
      - correspondence, 1949-1978, undated (Box 87, Folder 111)
      - minutes and reports, 1939-1944 (Box 87, Folder 112)
        - 1945-1949 (Box 87, Folder 113)
        - 1950-1953 (Box 87, Folder 114)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 87, Folder 115)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 116)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 117)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 118)
        - 1962-1966 (Box 87, Folder 119)
        - 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 120)
        - 1971-1980 (Box 88, Folder 121)
      - subjects, First Log Cabin Marker, 1959-1960 (Box 88, Folder 122)
      - yearbooks, 1966-1969, 1971-1977 (Box 88, Folder 123)
    - Officers, Treasurer, membership list, 1939-1979 (Box 88, Folder 124)
  - FRANCIS LATHAM, CA COLONY
    - General, charter, undated (Box 88, Folder 125)
  - GLENDALE, CA COLONY
    - General, by-laws, undated (Box 88, Folder 126)
      - minutes, 1954-1957 (Box 88, Folder 127)
        - 1957-1958 (Box 88, Folder 128)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 88, Folder 129)
      - yearbook, 1950 (Box 88, Folder 130)
  - GLENS FALLS, NY COLONY
    - General, gravestone inscriptions, in and nearby Hartford, NY, undated (Box 88, Folder 131)
      - yearbook, 1949-1950 (Box 88, Folder 132)
  - GREEN MOUNTAIN, VT COLONY
    - General, meeting announcements, 1986-1987 (Box 88, Folder 133)
  - GOLDEN GATE AREA, CA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 134)
  - HANNAH DUSTIN, CT COLONY
    - General, constitution, 1936, by-laws, 1938 (Box 88, Folder 135)
      - histories, 1937-1944 (Box 88, Folder 136)
      - memorabilia, undated (Box 88, Folder 137)
      - minutes, 1936-1951 (Box 88, Folder 138)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1947, 1951 (Box 88, Folder 139)
      - Treasurer, membership lists, 1939-1950 (Box 88, Folder 140)
  - HANNAH HENDEE, VT COLONY
    - General, constitution and by-laws, 1954-1975, undated (Box 88, Folder 141)
      - certificates, programs, 1975-1978, 1981, undated (Box 88, Folder 142)
      - history, ritual, 1961, undated (Box 88, Folder 143)
      - minutes, 1961-1964 (Box 88, Folder 144)
        - 1965-1967 (Box 88, Folder 145)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 88, Folder 146)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 147)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 148)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 89, Folder 149)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 89, Folder 150)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 89, Folder 151)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 89, Folder 152)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 89, Folder 153)
        - 1984-1986 (Box 89, Folder 154)
      - newspaper clippings, scrapbooks, 1961-1985, undated (Box 89, Folder 155)
      - photographs, 1971-1980, undated (Box 89, Folder 156)
      - yearbooks, 1970-1974, undated (Box 89, Folder 157)
        - manuscript, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 158)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1955-1969 (Box 89, Folder 159)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 89, Folder 160)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 89, Folder 161)
      - 1980-1983 (Box 89, Folder 162)
      - 1984-Sep 1985 (Box 89, Folder 163)
      - Oct 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 164)
      - undated (Box 89, Folder 165)
      - Treasurer, records, 1961-1976 (Box 90, Folder 166)
        - 1968-1971 (Box 90, Folder 167)
        - 1972-1976 (Box 90, Folder 168)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 90, Folder 169)
        - 1980-1986, undated (Box 90, Folder 170)
      - Registrar, records, 1959-1972 (Box 90, Folder 171)
        - 1973-1979 (Box 90, Folder 172)
        - 1980-1986 (Box 90, Folder 173)
        - undated (Box 90, Folder 174)
  - HARRISBURG, PA COLONY
    - Officers, Registrar, correspondence, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 175)
  - HIGHGATE, VT COLONY
    - General, constitution, by-laws, 1951, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 176)
      - minutes, 1947-1968 (Box 90, Folder 177)
        - 1969-1980 (Box 90, Folder 178)
      - scrapbook, 1948-c.1951 (Box 90, Folder 179)
        - 1948-c.1951, continued (Box 90, Folder 180)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1931,1952,1959 (Box 91, Folder 181)
      - Treasurer, financial records, 1976-1983 (Box 91, Folder 182)
        - membership list, c.1948-1972 (Box 91, Folder 183)
      - Registrar, membership lists, c.1931-1953, c.1957-1970 (Box 91, Folder 184)
  - HOUSTON, TX COLONY
    - General, charter, undated (Box 91, Folder 185)
  - ILLINOIS PRAIRIE, IL COLONY
    - General, charter, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 186)
    - Officers, Registrar, membership list, c.1969 (Box 91, Folder 187)
  - KANSAS CITY, KS COLONY
    - Officers, Registrar, correspondence, subjects, merger, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 188)
  - KANSAS CITY, MO COLONY
    - General, charter, 1929 (Box 91, Folder 189)
      - minutes, 1932-1937 (Box 91, Folder 190)
        - 1937-1941 (Box 91, Folder 191)
        - 1941-1942 (Box 91, Folder 192)
        - 1952-1962 (Box 91, Folder 193)
        - 1962-1972 (Box 91, Folder 194)
    - Officers, Treasurer, membership lists, 1944-1958, 1960-1968 (Box 91, Folder 195)
      - Registrar, annual reports, 1931-1973 (Box 91, Folder 196)
  - LAWRENCE, KS COLONY
    - General, charter, 1941 (Box 91, Folder 197)
      - minutes, 1941-1950 (Box 91, Folder 198)
        - 1950-1959 (Box 91, Folder 199)
        - 1959-1973 (Box 92, Folder 200)
    - Officers, President, correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 92, Folder 201)
      - Treasurer, membership lists, c.1942-1973 (Box 92, Folder 202)
  - LAWRENCEVILLE, NJ COLONY
    - General, history, 1933-1958 (Box 92, Folder 203)
      - minutes, 1941-1966 (Box 92, Folder 204)
      - scrapbook, 1935-1943 (Box 92, Folder 205)
        - 1945-1964 (Box 92, Folder 206)
  - MARYLAND, MD COLONY
    - General, by-laws, organizational minutes, list of charter members, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 207)
  - MERIDEN, CT COLONY
    - General, constitution, by-laws, 1951 (Box 92, Folder 208)
      - minutes, 1927-1929 (Box 92, Folder 209)
        - 1930-1936 (Box 92, Folder 210)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 92, Folder 211)
        - 1939-1943 (Box 93, Folder 212)
        - 1943-1945 (Box 93, Folder 213)
        - 1946-1954 (Box 93, Folder 214)
        - 1955-1971 (Box 93, Folder 215)
    - Officers, Registrar, correspondence, 1971, undated (Box 93, Folder 216)
  - MILWAUKEE, WI COLONY
    - General, by-laws, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 217)
      - minutes, 1953-1970 (Box 93, Folder 218)
    - Officers, Treasurer, reports, 1932-1970 (Box 93, Folder 219)
      - Registrar, annual reports (incomplete), 1941-1969 (Box 93, Folder 220)
        - correspondence, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 221)
  - MISSISSIPPI, MS COLONY
    - General, by-laws, organizational report, 1974, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 222)
  - MONTCLAIR, NJ COLONY
    - Officers, Registrar, membership list, 1902-1915 (Box 93, Folder 223)
  - MOUNTAIN TOP, NY COLONY
    - General, charter, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 224)
  - NEW HAVEN, CT COLONY
    - General, memorabilia, 1927, undated (Box 93, Folder 225)
  - NEW YORK CITY, NY COLONY
    - General, ballot, by-laws, 1915, 1932 (Box 93, Folder 226)
      - programs, 1896, 1900, 1909-1941, undated (Box 93, Folder 227)
  - OMAHA, NE COLONY
    - General, charter, 1940 (Box 93, Folder 228)
  - COLONY OF THE ORANGES, NJ
    - General, photographs, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 229)
  - PALM BEACH, FL COLONY
    - General, charter, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 230)
      - minutes, 1975-1979 (Box 93, Folder 231)
        - 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 232)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1975-1983 (Box 93, Folder 233)
      - Registrar, membership lists, 1973-1977, 1983, undated (Box 93, Folder 234)
  - PASADENA, CA COLONY
    - General, minutes, 1951-1965 (Box 94, Folder 235)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1942-1966 (Box 94, Folder 236)
      - Registrar, annual reports, 1941-1954, 1956, 1959, 1962, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 237)
        - membership list, notes, c.1929-1962 (Box 94, Folder 238)
  - PASSAIC, NJ COLONY
    - General, constitution, 1930 (Box 94, Folder 239)
  - PHILADELPHIA, PA COLONY
    - General, minutes, 1916-1921 (Box 94, Folder 240)
      - 1921-1929 (Box 94, Folder 241)
      - 1929-1931 (Box 94, Folder 242)
      - 1931-1936 (Box 94, Folder 243)
      - 1936-1940 (Box 94, Folder 244)
      - 1940-1946 (Box 94, Folder 245)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 95, Folder 246)
      - 1948-1957 (Box 95, Folder 247)
      - 1958-1966 (Box 95, Folder 248)
      - 1971 (Box 95, Folder 249)
      - notes, c.1956 (Box 95, Folder 250)
      - scrapbook, 1917-1940, 1925-1935, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 251)
      - yearbook, 1937-1938 (Box 95, Folder 252)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 95, Folder 253)
  - PHYLLIS LYMAN, DC COLONY
    - General, by-laws, 1960, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 254)
      - minutes, 1932-1935 (Box 95, Folder 255)
        - 1970-1976 (Box 95, Folder 256)
      - yearbooks, 1958-1968 (Box 95, Folder 257)
        - 1968-1974 (Box 95, Folder 258)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1965, 1969-1980, undated (Box 95, Folder 259)
      - reports, 1958, 1960-1961, 1975-1976, 1978, undated (Box 95, Folder 260)
      - Treasurer, financial records, 1971-1979, undated (Box 95, Folder 261)
        - reports, 1954-1958, 1961-1962, 1969-1970, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 262)
      - Registrar, membership lists, 1955-1956, 1964-1970, undated (Box 95, Folder 263)
  - PINELLAS, FL COLONY
    - General, by-laws and organizing minutes, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 264)
  - PITTSBURGH, PA COLONY
    - General, memorabilia, undated (Box 96, Folder 265)
      - minutes, 1905-1916 (Box 96, Folder 266)
        - 1916-1930 (Box 96, Folder 267)
        - 1931-1947 (Box 96, Folder 268)
        - 1947-1956 (Box 96, Folder 269)
        - 1956-1978 (Box 96, Folder 270)
    - Officers, Treasurer, annual reports, 1935-1948 (Box 96, Folder 271)
  - PLYMOUTH ROCK, CA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1937 (Box 97, Folder 272)
  - PORTLAND, OR COLONY
    - General, charter, 1927 (Box 97, Folder 273)
  - PRINCETON, NJ COLONY
    - General, by-laws and organizing minutes, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 274)
      - annual reports, 1950-1954 (Box 97, Folder 275)
      - minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 97, Folder 276)
        - 1953-1955 (Box 97, Folder 277)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 97, Folder 278)
      - Registrar, membership list, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 279)
  - PRISCILLA ALDEN, NY COLONY
    - General, certificate, 1922 (Box 97, Folder 280)
  - RUTHERFORD, NJ COLONY
    - General, minutes, c.1904 (Box 97, Folder 281)
  - ST. PAUL, MN COLONY
    - General, charter, 1907 (Box 97, Folder 282)
      - minutes, 1907-1915 (Box 97, Folder 283)
        - 1933-1936 (Box 97, Folder 284)
        - 1936-1940 (Box 97, Folder 285)
        - 1961-1965 (Box 97, Folder 286)
    - Officers, President, Round Robin reports, 1909 (Box 97, Folder 287)
      - Registrar, membership list, 1907-1950 (Box 97, Folder 288)
        - undated (Box 97, Folder 289)
  - ST. PETERSBURG, FL COLONY
    - General, yearbook, 1947-1948 (Box 97, Folder 290)
    - Officers, Registrar, annual reports, 1928-1959 (Box 97, Folder 291)
      - correspondence, 1947, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 292)
  - SAN DIEGO, CA COLONY
    - General, charter, undated (Box 97, Folder 293)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 97, Folder 294)
  - SAN FRANCISCO, CA COLONY
    - General, yearbook, 1933-1935 (Box 97, Folder 295)
    - Officers, Registrar, membership list, c.1905-1908 (Box 97, Folder 296)
  - SAN XAVIER, AZ COLONY
    - Officers, President, correspondence, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 297)
  - SANTA BARBARA, CA COLONY
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1961-1971 (Box 97, Folder 298)
      - Registrar, membership lists, 1961-1965 (Box 97, Folder 299)
  - SANTA MONICA, CA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1949 (Box 97, Folder 300)
  - SARAH BASSETT WHITE, NY COLONY
    - General, by-laws, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 301)
      - minutes, 1941-1944 (Box 97, Folder 302)
    - Officers, Registrar, correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 97, Folder 303)
      - membership lists, 1939, undated (Box 97, Folder 304)
  - SARAH SIBLEY, MI COLONY
    - General, by-laws and organizational minutes, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 305)
  - SPRINGFIELD, MA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1937-1938 (Box 97, Folder 306)
      - news clippings, 1938 (Box 97, Folder 307)
    - Officers, Registrar, annual reports, correspondence, 1955, 1964-1969 (Box 97, Folder 308)
      - membership list, 1937-c.1962 (Box 97, Folder 309)
  - SYCAMORE, IN COLONY
    - General, by-laws, 1981-1983, membership lists (Box 98, Folder 310)
      - agendas, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 311)
      - minutes, 1981-1986 (Box 98, Folder 312)
    - Officers, President, correspondence, 1983, 1986, undated (Box 98, Folder 313)
      - reports, 1981-1985 (Box 98, Folder 314)
      - Treasurer, correspondence and reports, 1981-1983 (Box 98, Folder 315)
      - Registrar, annual reports, 1982-1986 (Box 98, Folder 316)
        - correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 98, Folder 317)
  - TABITHA BROWN, NJ COLONY
    - General, minutes, 1940-1951 (Box 98, Folder 318)
      - 1952-1975 (Box 98, Folder 319)
    - Officers, General, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 98, Folder 320)
      - membership list, 1969-1975 (Box 98, Folder 321)
  - TAMPA BAY, FL COLONY
    - General, charter, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 322)
      - minutes, 1974-1980 (Box 98, Folder 323)
      - yearbook, 1977-1979 (Box 98, Folder 324)
    - Officers, Treasurer, correspondence andfinancial records, 1975-1981 (Box 98, Folder 325)
      - membership cards, 1974-1980 (Box 98, Folder 326)
  - THREE FLAGS, MO COLONY
    - General, charter, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 327)
  - TOLEDO, OH COLONY
    - General, minutes, 1941-1949, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 328)
      - 1956-1960 (Box 98, Folder 329)
      - 1960-1974 (Box 98, Folder 330)
      - records, c. 1901 (Box 99, Folder 331)
      - attendance, 1949-1960 (Box 99, Folder 332)
    - Officers, Treasurer, membership list, 1964-1977 (Box 99, Folder 333)
      - Registrar, membership list, 1906-1913 (Box 99, Folder 334)
  - TOPEKA, KS COLONY
    - General, charter, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 335)
  - VIRGINIA COMPANY, VA COLONY
    - General, by-laws, correspondence, membership list, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 336)
  - WAMPETUC, IA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 337)
    - Officers, General, list of officers, undated (Box 99, Folder 338)
  - WASHINGTON, DC COLONY
    - General, charter, 1927 (Box 99, Folder 339)
  - WESTERN PURCHASE, TN COLONY
    - General, by-laws, organization minutes, history, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 340)
  - WORCESTER, MA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1941 (Box 99, Folder 341)
  - WYCKOFF, NJ COLONY
    - General, charter, 1929, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 342)
  - YORK, PA COLONY
    - General, charter, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 343)
  - YORK COUNTY, ME COLONY
    - General, charter, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 344)
- MEMORABILIA AND OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Memorabilia
    - National-General
      - Memorabilia, gavel given by Cate Gilbert Wells (Box 100)
      - gavel given by Mrs. Solon Osmond Richardson of Toledo, OH (Box 100)
      - 75th anniversary card for the Clarke School for the Deaf, 1970 (Box 100)
    - National-Annual Congresses
      - Badges, 1934, 1935, 1937, 1940, 1941, 1945, 1947, 1955, 1958, 1959, 1963 (Box 100)
    - Colonies
      - Bronxville, NY Colony, banner (Box 100)
      - Hannah Dustin, CT Colony, gavel (Box 100)
      - New Haven, CT Colony, piece of Plymouth Rock (Box 100)
      - Pittsburgh, PA Colony, gavel (Box 100)
      - flag stands
        - NSNEW banner (Box 101)
        - NSNEW pole (Box 101a)
        - Pittsburgh, PA Colony, flags (Box 102)
  - Oversize Materials
    - National-General
      - Scrapbooks
        - The Clarke School for the Deaf, 1967 (Box 103)
        - Memories and Kurn Hattin, 1912-1954 (Box 103)
        - pictorial history, 1895-1970 (Box 103)
        - publicity clippings, 1945-1946
          - 1947-1948 (Box 103)
          - 1957-1960 (Box 103)
    - Colonies
      - Amsterdam, NY Colony
        - General, charter, 1929 (Box 104)
      - Anne Bradstreet, CA Colony
        - General, charter, 1939 (Box 104)
      - Baltimore, MD Colony
        - General, charter, 1955 (Box 104)
      - Cambridge, NY Colony
        - General, charter, undated (Box 104)
      - Champaign-Urbana, IL Colony
        - General, charter, 1936 (Box 104)
      - Elizabeth, NJ Colony
        - General, charter, 1928 (Box 104)
      - Frances Latham, CA Colony
        - General, charter, undated (Box 104)
      - Hannah Dustin, CT Colony
        - General, charter, 1936 (Box 104)
      - Hannah Hendee, VT Colony
        - General, charter, 1960 (Box 104)
      - Highgate, VT Colony
        - General, charter, 1929 (Box 104)
      - Houston, TX Colony
        - General, charter, undated (Box 104)
      - Kansas City, MO Colony
        - General, charter, 1929 (Box 104)
      - Lawrence, KS Colony
        - General, charter, 1941 (Box 104)
      - Palm Beach, FL Colony
        - General, charter, 1971 (Box 104)
      - Plymouth Rock, CA Colony
        - General, charter, 1937 (Box 104)
      - St. Paul, MN Colony
        - General, charter, 1907 (Box 104)
      - San Diego, CA Colony
        - General, charter, undated (Box 104)
      - Santa Monica, CA Colony
        - General, charter, 1949 (Box 104)
      - Sarah Bassett White, NY Colony
        - General, charter, 1939 (Box 104)
      - Springfield, MA Colony
        - General, charter, 1937-1938 (Box 104)
      - Sycamore, IN Colony
        - General, charter, 1981 (Box 104)
      - Tampa Bay, FL Colony
        - General, charter, 1975 (Box 104)
      - Topeka, KS Colony
        - General, charter, 1951 (Box 104)
      - Washington, DC Colony
        - General, charter, 1927 (Box 104)
      - Wyckoff, NJ Colony
        - General, charter, 1929 (Box 104)
      - York, PA Colony
        - General, charter, 1953 (Box 104)
      - York County, ME Colony
        - General, charter, 1949 (Box 104)
      - Boston, MA Colony
        - General, scrapbooks, 1932-1939
          - 1939-1955 (Box 104)
          - 1926-1933 1932-1939 (Box 105)
      - Bronxville, NY Colony
        - General, scrapbooks, 1914-1952
          - 1952-1955 (Box 105)
          - 1971-1974 (Box 105)
      - Brooklyn, NY Colony
        - Officers, Registrar, membership list, 1914-1936 (Box 105)
      - Evanston, IL Colony
        - Officers, Treasurer, membership list, 1959-1979 (Box 105)
        - Hannah Hendee, VT Colony (Box 106)